It's you again?
Oh, I'm sick of this, all right?
I'm not telling you
what you missed last week.
Seriously, I'm not doing it.
Fuck off.
I'm being deported next month.
I tried to flee up to Canada,
but they stopped me
at the border.
200 plus gas and tolls.
I'll get you
and your family across.
Hey, frank, can you
do me a favor
and bring me back
some Canadian Insulin?
It's 50% cheaper up there.
"Need the car to make money.
Thanks, Carl."
Youens got convicted.
Guilty on all counts.
- Oh, shit.
- This is officially stuck.
I know an Irish guy
that does wood stuff.
You want me to see
if he's around?
In 72 hours, you will be
free of your addiction.
How much do you need?
Can we do a little ransom sitch?
No, I get to stay.
Oh, fuck.
God damn it, v!
No fabric softener
in the girls' jammies.
Quick, kev, what else?
- What else, what?
- Besides fabric softener,
have I been a bad, bad girl?
- 0h.
- I called margo.
She's got another building
she's willing to lease.
No, fuck off, Fiona.
The answer's no.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I... I'm trying
to move forward here
and you're acting like
a fuckin' toddler.
I want things to be
okay between us.
They are.
I'm fired, but it was
100% worth it
to see the look on
that scumbag's face.
- Did we...
- Like, four times.
J'j' rock music if
j'j'j'j'j'j'
j'j' think of all
the luck you got j'j'
j'j' know that
it's not for naught j'j'
n you were beaming
once before if
j'j' but it's not like that
anymore j'j'
j'j' what is this downside j'j'
n” that you speak of? N”
j'j' what is this feeling j'j'
j'j' you're so sure of? N
j'j'j'j'j'j'
j'j' round up
the friends you got j'j'
j'j' know that
they're not for naught j'j'
n“ you were willing
once before j'j'
j'j' but it's not like that
anymore j'j'
j'j' what is this downside j'j'
n” that you speak of? N”
j'j' what is this feeling j'j'
j'j' you're so sure of? N
No. Oh, come on.
Uh... shut up!
Debs, get the fuck out!
Come on, I gotta take a leak!
J'j' rock music if
- what the fuck is going on?
- Well, debs
has been in there
for, like, an hour.
Well, tell her to get out,
franny's crying.
Yeah, I have been.
Debs, get the fuck out!
And who is ringing the bell?
It's 7:00 A.M.!
Howdy. That's for me.
Let's go, Liam.
Time to go to work.
Debs, I gotta take a leak.
- Gimme a minute.
- She's still in there?
Yeah.
N” you do what you like j'j'
all right, that's it.
I'm comin' in.
Jesus. I'll get franny.
Debs.
Shit.
You pregnant again?
Fucking better not be.
Fuck.
0h, debs, this one
says negative.
They all say negative.
How am I supposed to
trust any of them.
I haven't gotten my period yet.
Maybe it's just stress, right?
Or maybe the slut candy
didn't work.
- What?
- The morning after pill.
I can't afford franny right now,
never mind another stupid baby.
Negative? Liar!
Hi, got your child
to stop cryin'.
I got fired from my job, Fiona.
So don't be giving me shit
if I'm late
on my share of the house money.
Well, it's your turn
to buy groceries
- and make dinner tonight.
- I know.
Now get out so I can shower.
Ahh! Hey!
- What happened?
- That!
Shit.
- What's going on?
- What are you doing?
Ah, Jesus.
Now everyone's in here.
Guess I won't shower today.
Gonna get filthy anyway
cleaning that shitty building
my sister found
for homeless kids.
Oh, god, Ian.
Can't we be past this?
- Uh-huh.
- Can you get rid of him?
- Yes.
- You know what?
I'll just shower
at my apartment building.
I'm gonna go
to the store to swipe
- some more pregnancy tests.
- No, no, no.
I'm gonna take you
to planned parenthood.
We're gonna get a real test.
All right?
And you, you gotta sleep
at the bike shop
- from now on, okay?
- Fine.
Hey, I'm going to see
one of those sponsors later.
- Good. It's about fuckin' time.
- All right.
Hey.
Did you watch me pee, pervert?
That's whole lot of pee, babe.
- Hi.
- Who are you?
This is my friend kassidi.
That's my sister, Fiona.
I'm his girlfriend.
Check this out.
All Carl's.
- Wow.
- Yeah, I know, right?
Yeah, we gotta bounce. Let's go.
0h, right. See you later, sis!
Hey.
- You okay?
- Yeah, why?
Carl!
Because of that.
Holy shit.
Team, if I could have
your attention.
Uh, thank you for being here
this morning.
I want you to know that
just because
you look like terrorists,
doesn't mean you should
be treated like 'em.
Until america can distinguish
between good brown people
and bad brown people,
it's my goal to get you all
safely across the border
into Canada.
Shh, shh, shh.
Discretion, right?
You can all thank me later
when a big bull moose
is slurping an ice cold molson
right out of your butthole!
Okay, not an alcohol and sex
kind of a crowd.
I don't even wanna know
what's going on here, frank.
Entrepreneurship, Fiona.
You all right, Liam?
All right, good. Bye.
Anyhow, uh, my son Liam
will be taking a look
- at your notice to appear...
- Carl, I said no uber!
That's my car!
You can't just take it
whenever you feel like it!
God damn it!
N“ o Canada j'j'
m” our home and native land j'j'
everybody.
J'j' true patriot love if
Ii from all thy sons... j'j'
you don't know that, do you?
That would be a good song
for you to learn.
Liam, come here.
I'm gonna go deal with my
business in the front yard.
Get me one illegal from each
banned Muslim country.
- Yes?
- You got it, boss.
Peace out.
N“ o Canada j'j'
m we stand on guard for... n”
n“ 0 can... j'j'
- okay, here we go.
- Hey, frank.
- How are you?
- Can I get three Advair discs?
You bet. Bobby junior'll
be breathing easy
- in no time, grace.
- And it's costing me
half of what it costs down here?
Mm-hmm.
- Yes, sir.
- All right, give me
three months' supply of januvia,
100 tablets of Diovan,
10075 milligram pills
of praluent and you might as
well throw in two epipens.
Jesus, all that's for you,
Lionel?
I'm a walking medical disaster,
frank.
Well, that's why god
invented Canada.
Okay, everybody,
get your orders in.
Now, I'm giving you all
a low, low
special introductory price.
I can't be so generous
with my fees next time.
- Uh, you ready, Mauricio?
- Yeah.
Okay, you take a stool softener
with all that Vicodin.
You don't wanna end up
dead on the can like Elvis.
- Yeah.
- All right, who's next?
Found another razor blade.
I'll add it to the collection.
- This place is a dump.
- But we're gonna
- make it look great.
- Don't listen
to negative Nelly, okay?
He's still mad about the church.
Yeah, 'cause you got
pity-fucked by my sister
- with this building.
- Yeah, and she was really good.
I bet. She's great at
getting what she wants
and screwing everyone else.
Hey, Trevor, when do you think
we'll be able to crash here?
As soon as the city approves
our occupancy certificate.
I made a list of everyone
who may need a bed.
Tell me if I forgot anybody.
Ah.
You can take Jamie off here.
- Why?
- He's living at home I think.
What? Since when?
The other day, he tried
to kill himself
after his parents hauled him off
to some conversion church
or some shit.
Shit.
M ma na ma na j'j'
j'j' ba da ba ba da j'j'
m ma na ma na j'j'
j'j' ba da ba be if
j'j' ba da ba ba da j'j'
more scrambled eggs, my king?
Yes.
But this time, feed 'em to me.
Whatever you say, your highness.
Damn it, v!
- Is that too much?
- No, please, keep going.
Not with the fork.
You know how I want you
to feed 'em to me.
I'm sorry, sire.
N” bossa nova music if
that's what I'm talkin' 'bout.
J'j' ba ba be m
j'j' ba ba da ba da j'j'
what's taking so long?
I can feel the fetus
growing inside of me
as I sit here.
There's no way I'm letting
anything get in the way
of finishing welding school
and getting a good job.
Oh, so you'd get
the abortion this time?
Whatever it takes.
I'm not gonna be that mom
with three barefoot kids
hangin' off her Walmart cart.
If I have to get
that thing scraped out
or go on the pill
or get an iud up in me
or get castrated
right afterwards,
- I don't care.
- I think you gotta
grow balls first, debs.
Shit.
What?
Sierra's dude.
Debbie Gallagher?
About time.
Hey, good luck, debs.
Don't be pregnant.
It's open.
My family is driving me insane.
- Good morning.
- Every day, I wake up
to screamin' or cryin'
or fuckin'
or someone doin'
some crazy shit.
There's always strange people
in my house.
I know what you mean.
I can't keep track
of who's mad at me.
Or who I'm mad at.
Can't even use my own car.
Are we supposed to
feel bad for you?
- Yeah.
- Just move out.
Can't afford to.
Have you ever lived
on your own before?
Yes.
No. Not really.
So you're 28
and still living at home?
That's pathetic.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
There's an empty unit
you can move into
right downstairs.
- No, I need the money.
- That's just an excuse
people use when they're afraid
to have nice things
- for themselves.
- Okay, that's enough.
We gotta go to the witch doctor.
- Yes.
- The what?
Fertility guy.
- Oh. Okay.
- Come by tomorrow.
We're having a few people
over for happy hour.
Finish your coffee
and let yourself out.
Bye.
All right.
We're on our way, everybody.
Settle back, get comfortable.
How's the goat?
Let's play a little getting to
know each other alphabet game.
We'll go around,
we'll say our name,
where we're from
and something that we like.
And I... I'll start off, okay?
Uh, my name is frank.
I'm from the us of a.
And I like apples.
Okay, now it's your turn.
You... you repeat what I said
and then say something
about yourself.
My name is frank,
I am from the us of a
and I like apples.
That's what you say about me.
Say what about you?
My name, where I'm from
and what I like.
Your name, where you are from,
what you like.
No. God damn it.
Hey, point to me.
Point to me. Now repeat:
You are frank.
You're from the United States.
You like apples.
Okay, good.
Now, tell us your name,
where you're from
and something you like
using the next letter
of the alphabet.
- My name is sameer.
- Yeah. But don't point to me.
Point to you. You. Point...
I am from Yemen
and I like enab.
Enab?
I don't know... okay, but it's
gotta start with a b.
Uh, well, it does.
Uh, you see, e-n-a-b.
It's gotta begin with a b.
Enab begins with an e.
Not if you read right to left,
like in my country.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, fuck me.
This is gonna be along 16 hours.
- Hannah Campbell?
- Hey.
So?
Find out the test results
tomorrow.
Test cost 20 bucks.
Low income rate, my ass.
How 'bout no income rate?
- I need to get a job.
- Forgot my phone.
I'll be right back.
See, hold up.
Yo. All right,
this isn't what it looks like.
What, like you got
some other girl pregnant?
It happened when Sierra and I
weren't together.
Sierra know?
I haven't had a chance
to tell her yet.
It looks like you've had
nine months to tell her.
Things are good with me
and Sierra right now.
I don't wanna blow it.
All right, well,
you're gonna blow it
if you don't tell her.
I will.
All right, I should
get back in there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, Deb.
Hey, Jamie.
Hey, you guys.
My mom let you in?
Uh, no. We waited till she left.
Got you some burgers.
Came by to see
how you're feeling.
I've been better.
The drugs are pretty good,
though.
You guys like my new wristbands?
Um, do you need anything?
No, I'm... I'm good.
Hey, Geneva said you went
to some conversion church?
My parents found it.
Place over on Garfield.
This pastor turns homos
back to normal.
He says I'm so much of a fag
that I need more sessions
to be saved by god.
You don't need to be saved.
Yeah.
Right.
Yay! Well done, well done.
Okay, you're next, goat lady.
Bring it home.
Okay. Eh, your name is frank.
You are from the U.S.
And you like apple.
You are sameer
and you are from Yemen
and you like enab.
Ali from Iraq likes banam.
And you are adad from Syria
and you like, uh, samak.
And rania from Libya hkesjabbn
- yeah.
- My name is fatemeh
from Iran and I like juje.
Yes! We did it!
We did it, everybody!
I have no idea what
that crap you like is,
but everybody did really well.
It was a fun game,
Mr. Frank who likes apples.
J'j' oh oh ooh j'j'
j'j' oh ooh oh oh j'j'
j'j' oh oh ooh oh ooh oh oh j'j'
j'j' now I understand j'j'
n” this is who I am if
n“ 24 reasons to love me if
J'j' you'll never find one
as pure as me I!
N” 24 reasons
j'j' to love me j'j'
n“ na na na na na na j'j'
n“ na na na na j'j'
n” hey! Na na na na na j'j'
- m na na j'j'
- j'j' I got the 24 karat j'j'
j'j'j'j'j'j'
Oh, fuck!
Sorry, ehh, I left some tools.
- Okay.
- I still had your keys.
I was gonna leave them
on the counter when I was done
I shoulda called first.
No, that's fine.
I'm dressed. Kinda.
You live in here, now?
No, just takin' a shower.
Thanks for fixin' the door.
Looks great.
Mm-hmm.
Here's your keys.
So, uh, what are you
workin' on next?
I'm just going to a house
over on Franklin.
Owner saw some work on a Marion
mahony Griffin house.
A... who?
One of the world's first
female architects.
- Born in Chicago.
- Oh, wow.
You never heard of her.
- No.
- She worked with
frank Lloyd Wright.
Oh. I heard of him.
He stole most of her designs.
0h.
What a douche bag.
You ever seen
any of his buildings?
Uh, I don't know.
I don't think so.
They're all over the south side.
Really? I thought there was
just a bunch of
crack houses down here.
No. Some amazing historical
buildings in this area.
- Really?
- It's one of the reasons
I moved to Chicago.
Do you wanna see some of them?
Sure.
You like me.
Uh-huh.
How much?
A lot.
Oh.
Oh, god.
Oh, shit.
Are you doin' this?
Oh, my god.
There's someone in the back.
- So?
- Well, what if he sees?
He's got his earbuds in.
Fuck it, go faster.
J'j' rock music if
j'j'j'j'j'j'
- Barb?
- Oh, hey. Hi.
- Hey.
- How's it goin', man?
- All right.
- Have a seat.
Thanks. Uh, thanks for...
For meeting me, you know.
- Sure.
- Brad spoke very highly
of you, so.
So I... I didn't know I could
have a woman as a sponsor.
Oh, yeah. Anybody's a sponsor
as long as
there is no risk of falling in
love with that person.
Ah.
Well, you never know, right?
Ha! Fat chance, honey.
So...
What are we doing here?
Uhh, well...
I... I got some shit
goin' on, you know,
other than Brad falling
and I'm kinda
havin' a hard time with it.
And I got this professor,
he got carted off to prison.
- Mm.
- Um, then got this ex
who's dating this guy who got
some other girl pregnant.
I'm sorry, did I just walk into
an episode of gossip girl?
- What?
- I mean, why should I
care about some bitch, a guy,
a pregnant girl,
- jailbird teacher?
- I'm... I'm sharing, you know.
And what exactly does that
Blake lively whiney crap
gotta do with you?
It's what I'm going through.
What the hell you talkin'
about, man?
You're not going through
any of that crap.
I mean, you have convinced
yourself that you are.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah, so you don't have to
actually look at your own shit.
It's a fucking classic
codependence.
All right, what's your problem?
Halfway decent iookin' guy.
I'm assuming you're not
a complete moron, right?
Okay, um...
You know, maybe this isn't
a good match, huh?
Okay, well, you call me
when you're ready
to talk about you.
J'j' percussive music j'j'
j'j'j'j'j'j'
are we in Canada?
Not yet.
Now, we walk.
Yes.
J'j'j'j'j'j'
what's Canada like, Mr. Frank?
Well, it's wilderness
as far as the eye can see.
Filled with maple trees
that have an endless supply
of magical syrup
in their trunks.
I would like to try
magical syrup.
You will, fatemeh.
You will also receive
a pound of Canadian bacon,
a pair of ice skates
and a gift card to Tim hortons
as a welcome gift.
- Oh, wow.
- Wow!
Ah, if you thought lady Liberty
had a lot to offer,
wait till you see what
the lumberjack country
has in store for you.
Health care for all,
marriage equality for gays,
legal hookers for the asking.
Oh, I think I will enjoy Canada.
The canucks can be
a boring people,
but every now and again,
mother Canada spits out
a halfway decent talent
like bill shatner,
uh, Celine Dion,
um, Pamela Anderson,
- Justin bieber.
- [9asps}
oh, I would like to meet
Justin bieber.
Anything's possible.
That's why Canada's called
the new land of the free.
Ah!
Damn it, svet.
I just put new ice in that.
- Kevin, come clean this up.
- I got it.
No.
- What?
- You broke the glass,
you clean up the ice.
This is something you always do.
Exactly. So now it's your turn.
This is a man's job.
I don't think you're hearing me.
I'm not cleaning out the ice.
The ice will not be
cleaned out by me.
You broke the glass.
This is 50% your bar.
I've done the shit work
100% of the time.
That means you owe me
a bunch of times
to clean out the ice.
So go replace it
before a customer
gets glass in his drink,
cuts his throat open,
sues the bar, shuts us down
and then your ass
is back out on the streets.
I'm doing my lemons.
J'j' rock music if
j'j'j'j'j'j'
That was so hot.
I don't know what came over me.
Ohh, you're in full-on
domination mode.
Oh, yeah.
Something in me just snapped.
I'm tired of her controlling us.
You're making me so hot.
I'm making myself so hot.
J'j'j'j'j'j'
This is one of my favorite
buildings in the city.
- This place?
- One of the first
residential high-rise buildings
ever built.
No shit. I've walked past here
a thousand times.
Built as luxury apartments
for the Chicago exhibition
in the '30s.
I know a guy who got
his face shot off in here.
Arched windows.
It's romanesque revival.
Look at the ornamental cornice.
I would look at it
if I knew what a cornice was.
Up the top, there.
Come here.
J'j' rock music if
see all that extraordinary
masonry work and detail?
It's remarkable.
You mean the little
ribbon things?
It's polychromatic brick facade
on top of beautiful stone.
- Looks kinda like a castle.
- Yeah
this is the
frank Lloyd Wright thing?
Built for the robie family.
And the planters are supposed to
break the inside out
so it divides.
And we're under a bridge.
And now everyday places...
J'j'j'j'j'j'
Leviticus 20:13 says,
"if a man also lie with mankind
as he iieth with a woman,
both of them
have committed an abomination."
Praise the lord.
But we are here today
to give sweet Tammy
a chance to redeem herself
in the eyes of the lord
and return back to her flock.
Are you fuckin' kidding me?
Matthew 18 says we must
confront the sinner
and give him a chance to repent.
So, I ask you
in front of your family,
Tammy, do you
want to be cured of
the homosexuality disease
and go back
to being a normal girl again?
Yes.
Jesus.
Do you want god
back in your life, Tammy?
I do.
He can't hear you, Tammy.
Do you want god
back in your life?
Yes! Yes.
Then let us now close our eyes
and raise our palms to Tammy
so that we may light the path
for this lost lamb
to find her way back
to the kingdom of heaven
where she can become
the beautiful, feminine woman
with long hair
that she was put
on this earth to be.
Amen.
Oh, I'm gonna beat
the fuck out of this guy.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Romans, chapter 128.
M“ like baby, baby, baby,
ohh j'j'
j'j' like baby, baby, baby, no n
j'j' like baby, baby, baby,
ohh j'j'
- n I thought you... if
- oh, my goodness!
Fatemeh!
Fatemeh, are you okay?
- Can I have your goat?
- What happened?
She fainted.
This walk was too much for her!
When are we going
to get to Canada?
Yeah.
Calm down, she needs air.
Man was not meant
to hike in a burka.
Oh, wow. She's kind of pretty.
Yeah. I thought she was
a 70-year-old woman.
Uh.
What happened?
Where am I?
On your way to freedom.
Here you go.
- Yeah, thank you.
- May I, please?
- Yes.
- Here, I get.
- Oh.
- J'j' and I'm like baby, baby if
N baby, ohh u
j'j' like baby j'j'
- m baby, baby, ohh j'j'
- yalla.
Yalla, buddy.
J'j' rock music if
n hey, good lookin' j'j'
N“ you got me goin'
out of my mind j'j'
n“ you musta fell
from heaven, baby if
okay, now I'll do some
without my helmet.
- What?
- J'j' oh, that feelin' j'j'
j'j' chills runnin'
down my spine j'j'
how does my hair look?
I don't know. Red?
Just take the pictures.
What do you need these for?
I'm trying to get
some freelance welding work.
Abortions aren't cheap, Liam.
Remember that
when some skank tells you
she's on the pill.
You're pregnant?
I don't know yet.
Do I look sexy enough?
I guess.
These are great.
I look super hot.
Gonna put an ad on craigslist.
"Sexy welder girl
looking for work.
No job too big or too small.
Take some more with cleavage.
J'j' uh ba ba da be if
Hey.
- You okay?
- No.
Men are fucking assholes.
I'm...
Yeah, I'm sure
you guys can figure it out.
- What?
- I mean, it was probably
just an accident.
He murdered my mother.
Wh-who are you talking about?
My father. What'd you think.
Your father killed...
You never told me.
His parole hearing's
down at Pontiac correctional
first thing in the morning.
Charlie and I are driving
down there tonight,
but he's an hour late.
They let my father out,
I'm moving to Mexico.
- Hey, hey...
- You're late.
I'm sorry.
Yo. You didn't tell her
anything, did you?
No.
All right, but you got
a long drive ahead of you.
There's plenty of time
for you to do it.
There she is.
This is the place
you're restoring?
Yep. And I get to stay here
while I'm doing it.
- It's beautiful.
- Traditional craftsman.
Built in 1923. Greene and Greene
were influenced
by the English arts
and crafts movement.
You comin'?
Okay.
M“ near, far if
j'j' wherever you are n”
n“ I believe that the heart
will go on n“
- There she is.
- Canada?
The freedom falls.
She sits on the border
and keeps guard
over both countries.
Enough love in her cascading
waters to embrace
both of her children,
the United States and Canada.
- Let's go to Canada!
- We made it?
- Ahh!
- We are here!
- We made it!
- Freedom falls!
Freedom falls!
- Yalla, come on!
- I think I can take it
- from here, Mr. Frank.
- Yes.
J'j' uplifting acoustic music if
yalla!
Ah!
Ohh.
- You okay, yes?
- Much good.
J'j'j'j'j'j'
- gimme that.
- What are you doin'?
This place is kinda sketch, huh?
Next.
- Hi.
- Paperwork.
Forgot to sign
the declaration of need.
Here you go.
"By signing this form,
I declare that I am
in need of emergency food
and that my income
is below the poverty level."
Hm?
It's kinda humiliating,
don't you think?
Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
- I haven't been
to a food bank in a while,
do you have rotisserie chicken?
Next.
- Here you are.
- What is this stuff?
Beans, cheese and oatmeal.
What am I supposed to
make with it?
Use your imagination. Sir?
Paperwork.
I love all of the stained glass.
Yeah, they're typical
of these places.
It's what they call
arts and crafts houses.
- Cool.
- Come here, I wanna
show you somethin'.
Sit.
You won't be disappointed.
Okay.
Look up.
Oh, my god.
- Mm.
- Oh, that is awesome.
What is that made with?
Hand painted with gold leaf.
It's brilliant, huh?
Yeah, it is.
You're not kissing me back.
Mm.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no. Uh...
I'm sorry, I...
I thought you were single.
- I didn't see a ring.
- I am single.
My gaydar's usually better.
I'm not gay.
Wow.
I didn't mean to give you
the wrong impression.
You asked me to lie
on a bed with you.
Right. To look at the ceiling.
I'm sorry.
Ah...
No, no worries, I...
- I'm not looking for anything...
- No, I got it.
Complicated.
Complicated?
Your family and everything. You.
Me?
You're complicated.
0h.
Okay.
- Didn't mean it as an insult.
- No, I mean...
Being called complicated
feels...
Awesome.
I'm gonna go.
- I'll drive you back.
- No, it's okay.
I'll just, uh, uber.
Thanks for showing me around.
N” upbeat folk music j'j'
thank you.
Good luck, my friend. Good luck.
Your name is frank.
You are from the us of a,
- and you like apples.
- I knew you had it in you.
- Only took you 16 hours.
- Thank you, my friend.
Good luck, good luck.
Good-bye, soon to be
Mrs. Justin bieber.
Shukraan.
Easy, easy.
I owe you seven mile
piggyback ride.
I'm gonna hold you to it,
goat lady.
Thank you.
There you go. I got it.
Let me help you with the goat.
Come on, boy.
Uh, to you, buddy.
This thing's heavy.
Good luck to you.
Shalom, my friends.
That's all of 'em, Pierre.
I drop them to the safe house
and swing back
and take you to the pharmacy.
Merci beaucoup, amigo.
J'j'j'j'j'j'
Gonna miss those brown bunnies.
Mm.
Hey, Deb, did you get
your period yet?
No.
Smells disgusting.
It's free. Eat it.
Ah, there's no way
that's real cheese.
Carl doesn't like this, sis.
- Sis?
- I'm gonna postmates
kfc for him, who's in?
- Ah, me, sis.
- Thanks, sis.
- Thanks, babe.
- Eat it or don't eat it,
I don't care. It counts as
my groceries for the week.
Kfc will be here in 20 minutes.
- You rock.
- No, you do. Mm.
Oh, hell yeah!
I just got a welding job
for tomorrow!
"Sexy welder girl"?
Gotta go with your assets.
- Do we have a Bible?
- A Bible?
Yeah, the good book.
I doubt it.
Hey, can you believe that this
guy today told me
I was complicated?
Yes.
Are you serious? How?
Well, you married that guy
after, like, a week.
And you cheated on him with your
car thief ex-boyfriend.
Who had several different names.
Almost married a heroin addict.
Hid my meth inside
our dead mother's casket.
Didn't you also
get fired from a job
for fucking your boss' brother?
- Oh, yeah!
- Testified against me
to the military,
fired me, stole my church.
Wow, you found a Bible?
Okay, I get it. I'm complicated.
I'm gonna go walk my dog now.
Well, I can keep going.
Oh, fuck you guys.
At least rusty loves me.
This poor child
couldn't help himself
once the devil
got inside of him.
- Mm-hmm.
- Psalm 101:3 says,
"I will not look with approval
on anything that is vile.
I hate what faithless people do.
I will have no part of it."
Romans 13:8-10 says,
"let no debt
remain outstanding,
except the continuing debt
to love one another,
for whoever loves others
has fulfilled the law."
What is your name?
Ian...
- Gallagher.
- Are you a homosexual, Ian?
Indeed, I am.
Would you like to come up
to the altar
and bring Jesus
back into your life?
Oh, no. I'm... I'm good.
See, I already got Jesus
in my life.
Corinthians 6:9-10
clearly states,
"neither the sexually
immoral nor
male prostitutes nor homosexuals
will inherit the
kingdom of god."
- Amen.
- Oh, really?
'Cause colossians 3:11-13 says,
"here there is no Jew or
gentile, barbarian, scythian,
slave nor free, but Christ
is all, and is in all."
Corinthians 6:17-20,
"flee from sexual immorality.
All the sins a person commits
are outside of the body,
but whoever sins sexually,
sins against their own body."
Galatians 5:14,
"for the entire law
is fulfilled
in keeping the command:
Love thy neighbor as thyself."
The lust of the flesh comes
not from the father,
- but from the world.
- Woe to you,
teachers of law
and pharisees, you hypocrites.
You don't actually think
you can win
a Bible quoting contest with me.
He does.
Are you the queer boyfriend?
Oh, no, I'm queer transgender
ex-boyfriend, actually.
But we'll probably start
banging again soon.
Oh!
Hey, any of you queers
sick of this bullshit
wanna get out of here?
We got this brick building
over on Ashland.
It's the one with all the
gay rainbow flags.
- I'll go.
- Lewis.
Get back here.
Lewis! Get back here.
You wanna fight? I'll fight you,
but you're gonna get your ass
kicked by
a ho-mo-sexual.
Let's go.
Fags, this way!
- N“ la ah ah j'j' - no!
J'j' ooh, ooh, tonight j'j'
Steven you get over here,
right now.
J'j'j'j'j'j'
- lip?
- Yeah, yeah. Hey.
- Hey.
- Uh, thanks for meeting me.
Yeah, sure. You got it.
How long you been sober, kid?
Uhh, about a year.
- All right. Good for you.
- Thanks.
The food decent in this dump?
Yeah, it's not bad.
You buyin'?
- Okay.
- Great.
Okay.
Hey, so,
it's cool if I talk about
my ex-girlfriend a little bit?
You know, I got some shit
goin' on with her
and I guess I kinda wanna share.
- Oh, fuck yeah.
- Yeah?
You wanna talk about exes,
let me tell you about
the miserable cuntbag
of an ex that gave me
a cock suckin' venereal disease.
Women can't be trusted.
They're all assholes or whores.
I think I'll have
the cherry pie.
I'm all right.
J'j' near, far I:
J'j' wherever you are n”
n” I believe that the heart j'j'
j'j' will go on n“
j'j' once more n“
n” you open the door if
j'j' and my heart if
There you are, sweetheart.
Thank you for waiting.
J'j' rock music if
j'j'j'j'j'j'
Come on. Seriously?
Someone swiped my fuckin'
keys again!
Carl!
J'j'j'j'j'j'
No, I have to be serious
about my job right now.
I was just gonna hold your hand.
Okay.
Actually, do you mind putting
both hands on the wheel, please?
Yes, sure. Of course, ma'am.
Um, I'm sorry.
He's not your boyfriend.
You don't get to tell him
what to do.
This guy is the best driver
I have ever met.
He could operate this thing
with no hands
and just his dick
and get you there safely.
You can let me off right here.
But both hands are on
the wheel now, ma'am.
Let me out.
This chick is psycho.
Uh, ah.
What the hell?
You can't be pissing people off.
Jesus. Sorry.
Who the fuck are you?
Where's Denny?
We use Igor now.
Bullshit we use Igor now.
We've been using my buddy Denny
as the beer guy
since Stan was alive.
If he was such
a good buddy of yours,
you would've noticed
that I got rid of him
a year ago, and we use Igor now.
Well, as of this moment,
we're using Denny again.
Beat it, Igor.
I said beat it, Igor.
I'm... I'm gonna go.
What the hell did you just do?
You saw what I just did,
so why the fuck
are you asking me?
Meet you inside.
My man calls.
Here's your little psychopath.
J'j' rock music if
j'j'j'j'j'j'
Can you watch my daughter
a second?
Hell yeah!
It's about time.
You were awesome.
Uh, what?
What are you talking about?
Going at it with that pastor.
What... wait, what?
How do you know?
It's on YouTube.
It's already got,
like, 1,000 hits.
- Seriously?
- Uh-huh.
Thanks, man.
Yeah, no... no problem.
So what now?
I guess I gotta find you guys
a place to stay.
Guys wanna help me out?
Come on.
Thank you for meeting
with me, Ernest.
I wanted to talk to you about
maybe being my new sponsor.
Haven't had much luck
finding one.
I seem to upset people when I
bring up my ex-girlfriend,
but, uh, that's what's
going on with me.
You know, that's... that's
what I want to talk about.
Are you okay?
Ernest, your, um...
Your head is buzzing.
Sorry?
Okay.
Okay, you know what,
I'm gonna be right back.
You don't go anywhere.
All right? You stay here.
Hey, how'd the thing
with your dad go?
They don't decide right away.
I gotta go punch in.
- You tell her yet?
- It wasn't the right time.
When's the right time gonna be?
It's none of
your goddamn business.
No, fuck this, how 'bout I
fucking tell her then?
The fuck you will, man.
You guys are fighting?
I'm worried that
my deadbeat father's
gonna be released from jail,
and come after me
or Neil or Lucas,
and you're starting shit
with Charlie again?
Stay out of my life
and focus on your own shit, lip.
- Where you going?
- Home.
I thought you hated it there.
Changed my mind!
Okay. I'll see you tomorrow?
You're just gonna let me
go back home?
No, but I thought you wanted to.
Yeah, because you don't
love me anymore.
When did I say that?
When you yelled at me
for trying to
hold your hand in the car.
I didn't yell at you
for trying to hold my hand.
I yelled at you because
you scared a customer off.
You're yelling at me right now!
Because you're being crazy.
Where are you going?
I don't know!
Oh, my god, fucking headache.
Are you breaking up with me?
What?
Can we just go
back inside please?
Okay.
J'j' upbeat music j'j'
you made it!
- Hello.
I thought you were just having a
few friends over for happy hour.
- We're pregnant.
- Oh, my god!
Oh, my god, that's awesome.
- Thank you.
- Ah, here.
- Thanks.
- Oh, my god.
- Hi, Fiona.
- Hi!
- Hi.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you, honey, thank you.
- Hi... oh.
- Oh, hi, wow.
- Hi.
Happy Mel! Not used to that.
Babies make me giddy.
So which one of you
did the fertility treatment?
- Me.
- Except we're both pregnant.
Wait, what?
- Yeah.
- Shit.
- Yes.
How is that possible?
I'll give you a hint.
Wait, you had sex?
Like, dick sex?
It was the one and only time,
and it was awful.
Why did you do it then?
Increase our odds.
We couldn't afford ivf
for both of us, so...
Yeah, and she drew
the short straw.
And I fucking lost
my lesbian gold star.
Whose dick was it?
Ford's!
I-Irish Ford?
- Yes.
- He's the father?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, for both of us.
Get the fuck out of here.
- I know, yeah.
- Uh-huh.
And our kids are gonna look
just like that.
Mm!
Is that... that's one of Ford's?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
Jesus, how many
does this guy have?
Two others besides him.
He's the lesbian
spunk of choice.
Yeah, dude has primo sperm.
- O-Okay.
- Yeah.
That's good to know.
And there he is,
the man of the hour.
- Whoo! Whoo-whoo.
- Baby daddy!
Congratulations, daddy.
Thanks.
Have him put a baby
in you, too, Fiona.
Yeah, then we can all be
fat and pregnant together.
- Five kids, huh?
- Yeah.
It's getting a little
out of hand.
Well, at least you get
some action out of it.
It was humiliating.
She was hammered,
laughing the whole time.
Now who's complicated?
J'j'j'j'j'j'
Cheers.
Six hundred bucks
from the muslims,
750 off the meds.
Not bad for a couple
of hard days' work.
Where's my cut?
Here you go.
We are on our way to
financial independence, son.
Twenty bucks?
We finally found
a family business
that uses our god-given talents.
- How about 50?
- And, Liam, listen to me.
It's true what they say:
With a lot of hard work
and a little bit of luck,
you can make something of
yourself in america.
And we owe all of our success
to one person.
- Who's that?
- The twitterer-in-chief.
To false fear.
Fucking codependent, huh?
Couldn't stay away from me,
could ya?
Well, compared to everybody
else, you're not so bad.
Jesus, already falling
in love with me.
Look, um...
I don't know what to talk about.
You know, if I'm not talking
about someone else's drama.
General rule of thumb:
Their circus, their monkeys.
Just talk about yourself.
Yeah, I don't know
what that looks like.
It's okay.
Old Barb'll drag it
out of you soon enough.
So if you're gonna be
my sponsor,
then we gotta meet
at places like this?
Try some green goddess.
The fuck is in this?
J'j' upbeat music j'j'
j'j'j'j'j'j'
Where's the Sonic?
Sold it... time to
expand our business, son.
Let's get 'em loaded in.
- Come on, folks, welcome.
- This way.
Welcome, welcome.
We have a 16-hourjourney
ahead of us.
I'll help you.
We'll play a little
get-to-know-you game
as soon as you're
comfortably settled in.
J'j'j'j'j'j'
eh?
Boom.
What about the way I put
that beer guy in his place, huh?
Oh, that was hot, the way
you put Svetlana in her place.
I feel like I'm finally getting
my balls back from her.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
- Yeah!
- They're really turning me on.
Oh, yeah.
Sounds like you're getting
pushed out
of the picture, Natasha.
J'j'j'j'j'j'